<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mafiauto</string>
    <string name="intro_title">The night is dark...</string>
    <string name="intro_description">In the shadows, the mafia has awakened.\nWill you survive the chaos?</string>
    <string name="start_game">Start game</string>
    <string name="start_new_game">Start a new game</string>
    <string name="select_roles">Select roles</string>
    <string name="select_players">Select players</string>
    <string name="add_new_player_hint">Who are you... really?</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="previews">Previews</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="selected">Selected</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="player">Player</string>
    <string name="reveal_roles">Reveal roles</string>
    <string name="game_room">Game room</string>

    <string name="neutral">Neutral</string>

    <string name="god_father">Godfather</string>
    <string name="mafia">Mafia</string>
    <string name="joker">Joker</string>
    <string name="cult_leader">Cult Leader</string>
    <string name="doctor">Doctor</string>
    <string name="detective">Detective</string>
    <string name="civilian">Civilian</string>
    <string name="sniper">Sniper</string>
    <string name="silencer">Silencer</string>
    <string name="bomber">Bomber</string>
    <string name="bulletproof">Bulletproof</string>
    <string name="mayor">Mayor</string>
    <string name="oracle">Oracle</string>

    <string name="god_father_explanation">The Godfather is the mastermind of the Mafia — silent, ruthless, and always in control. While others carry out the dirty work, the Godfather gives the final word. No one suspects him, but he decides who dies.</string>
    <string name="mafia_explanation">A loyal servant of the Mafia, you operate in the shadows. Each night, you gather with your fellow killers to choose your next victim. Blood spills quietly, and fear spreads — just the way you like it.</string>
    <string name="doctor_explanation">The Doctor is the guardian angel of the town. Each night, they choose one person to protect — perhaps even themselves. When the Mafia strikes, the Doctor's hands may be the only thing keeping death at bay.</string>
    <string name="detective_explanation">The Detective hunts the truth in the shadows. Each night, they secretly investigate one player, searching for clues. A single discovery could tip the balance — but expose the Detective, and it may be their last case.</string>
    <string name="civilian_explanation">A Civilian has no special power — only their instincts and voice. They must survive the night, spot the liars, and guide the town through the storm. The darkness surrounds them, and they must stand tall.</string>
    <string name="sniper_explanation">The Sniper is a silent protector with one shot — and one chance. When the time is right, they can take a deadly risk to eliminate someone they believe is evil. But beware: one mistake can cost everything.</string>
    <string name="silencer_explanation">The Silencer is the voice of silence in the Mafia. Each night, they choose a target who will be muted the next day — unable to speak, unable to defend. Fear grows in the silence they leave behind.</string>
    <string name="bomber_explanation">The Bomber plays for no one but chaos. Their goal? Detonate and take others with them. Hidden in plain sight, they wait for the perfect moment to blow everything to hell.</string>
    <string name="bulletproof_explanation">The Bulletproof is no easy target. Armed with an unbreakable will and a hidden armor, they can survive a deadly attack — but only once. After that, the shadows close in like on anyone else.</string>
    <string name="mayor_explanation">The Mayor holds power in broad daylight. At any moment, they may reveal themselves and their vote will count double. A beacon of hope — or a dangerous misstep — depending on when they rise.</string>
    <string name="oracle_explanation">The Oracle peers into the beyond. If they die, their final vision reveals the alignment of one player. Death does not silence them — it speaks through them, one last time.</string>
    <string name="joker_explanation">The Joker doesn't care who wins — only that they lose. Their goal is chaos. If they’re executed by vote, they win the game instantly. So go ahead, accuse them... that's exactly what they want.</string>
    <string name="cult_leader_explanation">The Cult Leader whispers promises in the dark. Each night, they recruit a new follower. Their power grows in secret, consuming the town from within. By the time anyone notices, it's already too late.</string>
</resources>